♪Mighty winds carry me to the heavens♪
♪On a wild steed,
I sing, smiling at the mortal world♪
♪Then the cold night veils the stars♪
♪I fall to the depths, yet walk alone♪
♪I brave countless snowy peaks♪
♪Your lingering warmth still fills
my palm♪
♪Though frost and snow may bar my way♪
♪The light in my eyes will never fade♪
♪With a sword that cleaves the clouds♪
♪With a heart as firm as stone♪
♪Through all I've endured,
I have no regrets♪
♪I'm still the boy I once was♪
=Sword God=
=Episode 7=
I, Zhao Feiyang,
haven't been tested yet.
Zhao Feiyang,
didn't you hear what the elder said?
The trial is already over.
What are you even testing for?
Even if you take it,
you're just putting on a show.
Why waste everyone's time?
According to the rules,
every outer disciple has the right
to take the test.
Why can't I?
Zhao Feiyang,
I know it's been tough for you
all these years.
So there's no need to test.
Sect Master, what do you mean?
Considering your years of loyalty,
as long as you break no rules,
you can always stay here
as an outer disciple.
Sect Master, you can't!
No outer disciple
stays in our sect forever.
Won't that eat into everyone else's
cultivation resources?
Exactly!
Yeah.
Exactly.
Why should he?
Elder Wang,
(Heavenly Sword Sect)
Zhao Feiyang
has contributed to our sect before.
It's only natural for the Sect Master
to make an exception for him.
That's right.
Zhao Feiyang,
the Sect Master is giving you
one last bit of dignity.
Hurry and thank him.
Consider yourself lucky this time.
Dignity?
After three years,
what's left of my dignity?
Sect Master,
I don't need
this kind of dignity.
You...
Talk about ungrateful!
He just turned it down.
(Guess I can't stay here anymore.)
(I need another way
to repair my meridians.)
Wait!
Father,
let him take the test.
(Zhao Feiyang,)
(you can't leave.)
(If you go,)
(how can you witness my rise?)
Zhao Feiyang,
go ahead and take the test.
Even if you fail,
our sect will still wish you
a bright future.
Thank you, Sect Master.
Enough.
Hurry up and take the test!
(Just what grade)
(is the Dao Bone in me?)
(I'll use the testing stone
to find out.)
Yellow?
Impossible.
Anything wrong with the testing stone?
He had yellow talent three years ago.
After three years of being powerless,
he still has yellow talent.
That's unbelievable!
No wonder he insisted
on taking the test.
So he was confident all along.
Three years of biding his time...
Is he finally turning things around?
Not bad.
Biding your time
and building up your strength.
Zhao Feiyang,
you've truly impressed me.
(Zhao Feiyang,)
(I knew you never gave up.)
(But you're still far behind me.)
Enough. No more testing.
You are now a formal disciple.
What's the rush?
It's not over yet.
♪With a sword that cleaves the clouds♪
♪With a heart as firm as stone♪
♪Through all I've endured,
I have no regrets♪
What?
Oh my...
Could it be...
Am I dreaming?
♪Every wound, every ache♪
♪I turn them all into strength♪
♪Even if fate is fickle♪
♪And breaks my wings♪
♪I will take to the sky♪
♪And bravely fly once more♪
♪Look at this blade of mine♪
♪Still shining cold and bright♪
♪The fire in me burns even wilder♪
♪No matter what, I won't yield♪
♪Let all the world♪
♪Remember my face♪
That is...
A True Dragon?
No...
No way.
Absolutely impossible!
With his unranked Dao Bone
and Stage 1 of the
Body Tempering Realm,
how could he make the spirit stone
glow black?
But the truth is right before us.
We all saw it.
We're about...
about to see his Dao Bone
and cultivation level!
(Zhao Feiyang,)
(no wonder you looked down on me.)
(You've been hiding your strength!)
(Body Tempering Realm, Stage 9)
Stage 9?
What...
He was only at Stage 1 yesterday.
Today he's already at Stage 9?
How...
how did he pull that off?
(Body Tempering Realm, Stage 9)
But at his age,
this level of cultivation
shouldn't make the spirit stone
emit black light.
Maybe the Dao Bone he obtained
is no ordinary one?
(Body Tempering Realm, Stage 9.
Dao Bone Grade...)
What's going on?
Why is it so hard
to tell his Dao Bone grade?
Yeah.
Wang,
is something wrong with
your precious spirit stone?
No way.
It's always worked perfectly
for nearly a century.
It can't just go wrong.
(Why can't the Dao Bone grade
be revealed?)
(Maybe I'm not using enough power?)
My precious stone!
How could this happen?
The testing stone...
is broken!
Your precious stone is broken now, huh?
Zhao Feiyang,
I'm furious!
Get out of here at once!
Leave this sect!
I made the spirit stone shine.
According to the rules,
I should be a formal disciple now.
Why should I leave?
Can't you see my testing stone
is already broken?
Your Dao Bone grade
wasn't displayed at all!
Exactly.
Otherwise, at his current level,
making the spirit stone glow black
would be unbelievable.
I see.
I thought Heaven was blessing us again.
(Looks like it was a false alarm.)
But I'm at Stage 9
of the Body Tempering Realm.
Everyone saw it, right?
Well...
Exactly.
You?
Going from Stage 1 to Stage 9
in one day?
Impossible!
The test result isn't reliable.
Are you saying
all the previous results
weren't reliable?
Well...
The previous results were reliable.
But Cuihua's astonishing test
further damaged
the spirit stone.
So it malfunctioned during your test,
and eventually broke.
That makes sense.
Exactly.
So you doubt my cultivation?
Then
test me yourself.
Sure.
Since you put it that way,
I won't refuse.
Nonsense.
No private duels among fellow disciples!
Sect Master,
the testing stone malfunctioned.
That's on me.
Since Zhao Feiyang claims
his cultivation is genuine
and he wishes to stay
as a formal disciple,
why not let them spar
and see if he's telling the truth?
Sect Master,
if Zhao Feiyang's truly capable
of rising from Stage 1 to Stage 9
in one day,
despite his unranked Dao Bone,
his future
is still promising.
Very well.
Then,
you two may spar.
Wang Jie,
your cultivation is higher than his.
Don't use your full strength.
Yes, Sect Master.
I know how far to go.
Zhao Feiyang,
I'm at Stage 2 of the
Spirit Awakening Realm.
You're only at Stage 1 of the
Body Tempering Realm.
I'm more than a full realm above you.
But don't worry.
I'll only use ten percent of my strength
to expose your little act.
Enough talk.
Make your move.
You're asking for it!
He's that strong?
He actually blocked it?
Yeah.
What...
He's so powerful?
No way.
Am I seeing things?
Senior Brother Wang was forced back?
You're not seeing things. It's true.
No wonder he was once
the chief disciple.
He's still got real skill.
Junior Brother Wang,
what are you doing?
Stop playing around.
(What's going on?)
(I said I'd only use ten percent,)
(but I actually used fifty percent.)
(Yet he actually knocked me back.)
(Is he really at Stage 9?)
Wang Jie underestimated him.
Wang Jie,
don't waste any more time.
Zhao Feiyang's been here
for seven years.
He's no slouch in a fight.
You won't beat him
using only ten percent.
Raise it to thirty percent now.
Understood.
Zhao Feiyang,
I won't hold back anymore.
(Don't blame me!)
(I'll use all my strength)
(and give you a good beating!)
(He's a whole major realm above me.)
(But if I don't prove myself today,)
(everyone will keep thinking)
(I'm a useless pushover.)
Senior Brother Wang can't lose.
Senior Brother Wang's
Mountain-Shifting Palm
reached minor mastery six months ago.
Zhao Feiyang's in trouble now.
(Can you believe it?)
(Three years ago,)
(he was our sect's chief disciple.)
(But now,)
(he's like a stray dog.)
Mountain-Shifting Palm!
What...
He's coughing blood!
He's only humiliating himself!
What a fool.
He took Wang Jie's
Mountain-Shifting Palm head-on.
Doesn't he know his limits?
Zhao Feiyang,
you can't hold a candle to me.
Keep training...
Senior Brother Wang!
Why did he fall?
He's injured internally.
He passed out.
♪I once stood on high,
drawing spiritual energy into my blade♪
♪I laughed, pointing at the stars,
young and fearless♪
♪Then came my fall,
with frost and snow on my shoulders♪
♪My Dao foundation was damaged,
yet my Dao heart never wavered♪
♪I crossed countless peaks
to find my answer again♪
♪Through endless trials,
my Nascent Soul came♪
♪Heaven and earth my furnace,
I rose from the flame♪
♪No sword in hand,
yet numberless blades obey♪
♪I seek the Dao beyond the clouds♪
♪Unafraid of countless trials♪
♪With this flesh and soul♪
♪I shall forge a new age♪
♪Let thunder and fire crown me♪
♪Let wind and clouds heed me♪
♪At cultivation's peak♪
♪My first resolve remains unchanged♪
♪The sun and moon turn♪
♪I hear the Great Dao ring♪
♪I am the undying flame♪
♪Looking back when dust settles♪
♪At last I see, immortality♪
♪Lives in your smiles.♪